<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cluj-Napoca Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Food</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="coffee">Coffee \nShops</string>

    <!-- Parks category -->
    <string name="central_park">Central Park</string>
    <string name="description_central_park">The Central Park is one of the main green spaces in
        Cluj-Napoca, founded in 1827. Full of green, a lake and a casino, the park is one of the
        main attractions of the city. Over spring and summer, the lake is populated with swans and
        ducks, which are a delight for children. By the lake, there is also the Centre of Urban
        Culture, a historic monument that played the role of casino, museum, school of fine arts and
        restaurant over the years. In most recent years, either in the Casino\'s building or the park
        alleys, cultural and recreational events play a big role. Either if you want to participate
        at a dance course, ride the bike, attend the UNTOLD Festival or just sit on a bench, the
        park always manages to bring you into a relaxing state. </string>
    <string name="address_central_park">Cardinal Hossu Iuliu Street, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_central_park">Opened for public non stop</string>
    <string name="phone_number_central_park">+40 720 425 741</string>

    <string name="botanical_garden">Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="description_botanical_garden">Is a botanical garden located in the south part of
        the city and was founded in 1872. Bedides being a tourist destination, the garden also
        serves as a teaching and research center as part of the Babeș-Bolyai University. The
        garden is over 14 hectares in area, with over 10,000 plants from throughout the world.
        The main attractions are the Japanese Garden (a garden in Japanese style, with a brook and a
        Japanese-style house) and the Roman Garden with archeological remains from the Roman colony of
        Napoca.</string>
    <string name="address_botanical_garden">Republicii Street, number 42, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_botanical_garden">Monday to Sunday from 8 AM to 8 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_botanical_garden">+40 264 592 152</string>

    <string name="cetatuie_hill">Cetățuie Hill</string>
    <string name="description_cetatuie_hill">This is the place to go to if you want to admire one of
        the best panoramas of the city and the surrounding hills, rivers and even mountains. The
        fortress was built in the 18th century, in order to ensure the control of the city, more
        than for defensive purposes, occasionally serving as a prison. </string>
    <string name="address_cetatuie_hill">Gruia Street, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_cetatuie_hill">Opened for public non stop</string>

    <string name="hatieganu_park">Iuliu Hațieganu Sports Park</string>
    <string name="description_hatieganu_park">Mostly known by its old name, the Babeș Park is one
        of the biggest parks of Cluj-Napoca and at the same time it is also the campus of the
        Faculty of Physical Education and Sport within UBB. Established in 1931, the park wss
        designed to be the place of sports training to university students, but also an oasis of
        tranquillity and balance, accessible to everyone. The park combines authentic natural spaces
        with perimeters for sports activities.</string>
    <string name="address_hatieganu_park">Pandurilor Street, number 7, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_hatieganu_park">Monday to Sunday from 6 AM to 11 PM</string>

    <string name="iulius_park">Iulius Park</string>
    <string name="description_iulius_park">Iulius Park is an oasis of relaxation in the city. It
        offers visitors the most enjoyable recreation and disconnection modes in nature through
        pedestrian overpass, cycling and treadmill, alleys promenade and relaxation areas equipped
        with benches. You can either relax on the green areas or go by the lake and watch the swans
        and ducks.</string>
    <string name="address_iulius_park">Vaida Voevod Alexandru Street, number 53B, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_iulius_park">Opened for public non stop</string>

    <string name="adrenalin_park">Adrenalin Park</string>
    <string name="description_adrenalin_park">Adrenalin Park is the first adventure park from
        Cluj that offers aerial games, team buildings, parties, company events and kids theme events.
        With 12 adrenaline paths, the park is designed so that both children and adults can enjoy,
        together with nature and movement. There are 98 games, including 30 games for kids.</string>
    <string name="address_adrenalin_park">Casele Micești, number 152F, Feleacu</string>
    <string name="schedule_adrenalin_park">Monday to Friday from 12 PM to 8 PM
        \nSaturday and Sunday from 10 AM to 8 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_adrenalin_park">+40 371 040 434</string>

    <!-- Hotels category -->
    <string name="hampton_hotel">Hampton by Hilton</string>
    <string name="description_hampton_hotel">Conveniently located just two minutes from downtown
        Cluj, the hotel is only a 10-minute drive from Cluj-Napoca International Airport and within
        walking distance of businesses centers including The Office, Maestro, Power, Silver and
        Julius Business Centers.</string>
    <string name="address_hampton_hotel">21 December Street, number 67, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_hampton_hotel">Non stop</string>
    <string name="phone_number_hampton_hotel">+40 372 725 566</string>

    <string name="golden_tulip_hotel">Golden Tulip</string>
    <string name="description_golden_tulip">Located only a few minutes away from downtown Cluj-Napoca,
        the hotel tends to impress with its superb urban view. Close to shopping malls, business
        centers and recreation areas, it is the perfect choice for leisure or business travel.</string>
    <string name="address_golden_tulip">Observatorului Street, number 129, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_golden_tulip">Non stop</string>
    <string name="phone_number_golden_tulip">+40 264 545 000</string>

    <string name="grand_italia_hotel">Grand Hotel Italia</string>
    <string name="description_grand_italia">Located just 5 minutes from the old town center and at
        only 20 minutes from International Airport of Cluj-Napoca. It is the ideal place to taste
        the delightful charm of Transylvania, while benefiting from high class service throughout
        the stay.</string>
    <string name="address_grand_italia">Trifoiului Street, number 2, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_grand_italia">Non stop</string>
    <string name="phone_number_grand_italia">+40 364 111 333</string>

    <string name="ramada_hotel">Ramada Hotel</string>
    <string name="description_ramada_hotel">It is located 5 minutes walk from the business, tourist
        and historical center of Cluj-Napoca. Ramada Hotel is the perfect option, both for business
        and leisure purposes. It has an entire executive floor with access to Executive Lounge
        facilities and panoramic terraces.</string>
    <string name="address_ramada_hotel">Calea Turzii, number 43&#8211;49, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_ramada_hotel">Non stop</string>
    <string name="phone_number_ramada_hotel">+40 372 743 143</string>

    <string name="belvedere_hotel">Belvedere Hotel</string>
    <string name="description_belvedere_hotel">The hotel is situated in the central area of ​​
        Cluj-Napoca, on the Cetatuie hill. Its location offers its guests a great panorama and
        access to a lot of important tourist attractions (Art Museum, St. Michael\'s Church, Banffy
        Palace, Matei Corvin Statue) as well as various public institutions (Cluj-Napoca City Hall,
        Student Culture House).</string>
    <string name="address_belvedere_hotel">Călărașilor Street, number 1, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_belvedere_hotel">Non stop</string>
    <string name="phone_number_belvedere_hotel">+40 264 432 071</string>

    <!-- Food category -->
    <string name="samsara_food">Samsara Foodhouse</string>
    <string name="description_samsara_food">Samsara is the only specialized vegetarian and vegan
        restaurant in Cluj (at least until today). They offer healthy and tasty meals and drinks at
        their location as well as a delivery service that covers the entire city.</string>
    <string name="address_samsara_food">Ștefan Ludwig Roth Street, number 5, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_samsara_food">Monday to Sunday from 11 AM to 11 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_samsara_food">+40 799 073 073</string>

    <string name="jaxx_food">Jaxx</string>
    <string name="description_jaxx_food">This american restaurant makes visitors start feeling the
        real atmosphere that is completed by the tables and decorations inspired by great American
        Rock Bands, the car on top of the bar, and the real chopper from the wall. These are all
        part of the rock spirit that catch everybody that enters the restaurant.</string>
    <string name="address_jaxx_food">Emil Isac Street, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_jaxx_food">Monday to Friday from 10 AM to 1 AM
        \nSaturday and Sunday from 12 PM to 2 AM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_jaxx_food">+40 756 136 953</string>

    <string name="joben_food">Joben Bistro</string>
    <string name="description_joben_food">Embark yourself in a trip away from conventional
        design and discover the marvellous world of fiction. The fantastic pub, mystically protected,
        takes you back in time. The universe of Jules Verne, filled with fantasy and sci-fi stories
        pops-up. </string>
    <string name="address_joben_food">Avram Iancu Street, number 29, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_joben_food">Monday to Friday from 7:30 AM to 1 AM
        \nSaturday and Sunday from 12 PM to 3 AM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_joben_food">+40 720 222 800</string>

    <string name="baracca_food">Baracca</string>
    <string name="description_baracca_food">Located in downtown Cluj-Napoca, this restaurant is the
        place where architecture, design and passion for life, offer the perfect setting to
        demonstrate love for gastronomy and quality ingredients. Baracca is the place where life is
        celebrated every moment.</string>
    <string name="address_baracca_food">Napoca Street, number 8A, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_baracca_food">Monday to Sunday from 12 PM to 11 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_baracca_food">+40 732 155 177</string>

    <string name="klausen_food">Klausen Burger</string>
    <string name="description_klausen_food">It is a micro brewery with a restaurant and a roof top
        terrace that has a wonderful view over the city. Located in the center of the city, the
        restaurant is best know for its beer. Klausen Burger Beer is made in front of customers and
        produced only with imported raw materials.</string>
    <string name="address_klausen_food">Ferdinand Street, number 22, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_klausen_food">Monday to Friday from 10 AM to 2 AM
        \nSaturday and Sunday from 10 AM to 3 AM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_klausen_food">+40 372 717 552</string>

    <string name="fabrica_food">Fabrica de bere Ursus</string>
    <string name="description_fabrica_food">2011 marks the date of opening a craft Mini-Brewery
        in Cluj-Napoca, on the location of the old brewery, however in a very special format, the
        brewery being a place where people in Cluj-Napoca can watch how fresh beer is brewed.
        The craft Mini- Brewery is actually named \"Fabrica de Bere Ursus\", and the intense
        experience of the craft beer specialties produced in this location is being described
        as \"Pure, Unfiltered Art\". The location is also a restaurant, the food that is being served
        is complementing the local beer. </string>
    <string name="address_fabrica_food">Calea Mănăștur, number 2&#8211;6, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_fabrica_food">Monday to Saturday from 8 AM to 3 AM
        \nSunday from 8 AM to 12 AM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_fabrica_food">+40 756 393 333</string>

    <string name="maimuta_food">Maimuța Plângătoare</string>
    <string name="description_maimuta_food">This restaurant has an exciting and mysterious
        history, having 88 years old. Even though now it is a restaurant, the place formally was a
        pub where people used to go and drown their bitter. The owner was a fat man who tended to
        cry whenever he was drinking. His suffering and misfortune was due to a local competitor,
        opened not very far away. The owner was known to the employees for his \"tear-concerts\".
        At a soda supply, a restaurant employee was talking to the distributor about the owner,
        mentioning that he is \"Wailing like a crying monkey\". The owner heard this and since then,
        he decided to change the name of the restaurant to \"Crying monkey\". Nowadays, the
        restaurant is trying to adapt by making not very sophisticated dishes and making available
        more than 140 wine labels to their customers.</string>
    <string name="address_maimuta_food">Sindicatelor Street, number 1, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_maimuta_food">Monday to Friday from 8 AM to 11 PM
        \nSaturday and Sunday from 9 AM to 11 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_maimuta_food">+40 756 157 433</string>

    <string name="euphoria_food">Euphoria Biergarten</string>
    <string name="description_euphoria_food">Having a dream location, on Canalul Morii, close to
        the centre of the city and the Central Park, the restaurant has an atmosphere that attracts
        everybody as soon as the threshold is crossed. From traditional dishes to the most
        sophisticated dishes, the menu is one of the strengths of the Euphoria Biergarten
        restaurant. Besides this, Euphoria Biergarten also hosts an impressive collection of beer
        mugs collected from all corners of the world and exposed inside as true museum objects.</string>
    <string name="address_euphoria_food">Cardinal Iuliu Hossu Street, number 25, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_euphoria_food">Monday to Sunday from 8 AM to 2 AM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_euphoria_food">+40 756 393 333</string>

    <string name="livada_food">Livada</string>
    <string name="description_livada_food">Placed in a historical house and being surrounded by a
        beautiful garden, the restaurant offers a balanced and varied menu, which includes a range
        of products by Chef Patrizia Paglieri, a selection of good wines and quality live music.
        The decorative elements are inspired by the music and nightlife of a  classic Scottish pub.
        The warm atmosphere of the restaurant and the attraction brought by the terrace bring an
        oasis of tranquility in the heart of the city.</string>
    <string name="address_livada_food">Clinicilor Street, number 14, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_livada_food">Monday to Friday from 11 AM to 12 AM
        \nSaturday and Sunday from 12 PM to 12 AM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_livada_food">+40 722 111 115</string>

    <string name="carrousel_food">Carrousel By Chios</string>
    <string name="description_carrousel_food">Privileged to have a central location, in the Central
        Park, Chios and Carrousel remain a symbol of Cluj-Napoca. Starting with a modern design,
        inspired by current trends, the restaurant is a unique place where the delightful Chios
        Lake panorama can be admired and the history and architectural beauty of the old Skating
        Pavilion can be enjoyed. Using almost exclusively locally sourced ingredients, Carrousel
        proposes a unique and novel fusion menu, in which the Chefs creatively combine the strong
        traditional romanian cuisine roots with the refined elements of french cuisine and the
        mediterranean accents of italian cuisine in a blend that delivers authentic, quality dishes.</string>
    <string name="address_carrousel_food">George Coșbuc Street, number 14, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_carrousel_food">Monday to Sunday from 12 PM to 12 AM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_carrousel_food">+40 753 059 359</string>

    <!-- Coffee shops category-->
    <string name="coffee_addicts">Coffee Addicts</string>
    <string name="description_coffee_addicts">Located in the center of the city, Coffee Addicts is
        the place where coffee lovers and addicts are understood and always welcome. Whether you
        want to recharge your batteries or just enjoy a good cup of coffee, the baristas are happy
        to guide each and every customer to the perfect combination of flavours.</string>
    <string name="address_coffee_addicts">Strada Regele Ferdinand, number 9, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_coffee_addicts">Monday to Friday from 7:30 AM to 6:30 PM
        \nSaturday and Sunday from 10 AM to 3 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_coffee_addicts">+40 744 937 340</string>

    <string name="q_caffe">Q Caffe</string>
    <string name="description_q_caffe">Q Caffe is a bohemian café in the heart of Cluj, with good
        music and a friendly ambience in a magical setting. Q Caffe is a place with a special story
        about people being one of the oldest and most popular cafes in Cluj, opened for 10 years. </string>
    <string name="address_q_caffe">Maior Petru Street, number 13, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_q_caffe">Monday to Sunday from 7:30 AM to 3 AM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_q_caffe">+40 752 104 641</string>

    <string name="teo_cafe">Teo\'s cafe</string>
    <string name="description_teo_cafe">The coffee shop starts preparing the coffee from an espresso
        and according to the state and the desire of the customers, the baristas make magic and
        personalize the coffee. Believing in the concept that \"a good day is known since it starts\",
        the coffee shop owners think that the perfect day is accompanied by the coffee each person likes.
        Coffee stimulates, raises our motivation and the processing of information. Being present
        since 2010, it has 8 locations across Cluj-Napoca and Iași, and is known for the
        friendliness of baristas. </string>
    <string name="address_teo_cafe">Memorandumului Street, number 26, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_teo_cafe">Monday to Friday from 7 AM to 6 PM
        \nSaturday from 10 AM to 3 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_teo_cafe">+40 754 929 221</string>

    <string name="narcoffee">Narcoffee Roasters</string>
    <string name="description_narcoffee">It is a coffee chain which seeks to democratize true,
        balanced coffee. At Narcoffee, everything revolves around coffee, black or with milk, served
        in the place or to go. The focus is on specialized coffee, with no syrups or other
        artificial flavours. Bringing coffee from different corners of the world, they fry it
        locally, and then serve it freshly ground to those curious to taste more.</string>
    <string name="address_narcoffee">Eroilor Bulevard, number 49, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_narcoffee">Monday to Friday from 7:30 AM to 6 PM
        \nSaturday and Sunday from 9 AM to 8 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_narcoffee">+40 722 571 290</string>

    <string name="phil_coffee">Phil\'s Coffee Shop</string>
    <string name="description_phil_coffee">The coffee shop that makes you PHIL good. Sometimes, the
        only thing needed in the morning is a delicious coffee and a fresh croissant. The coffee
        shop offers the perfect environment to start the day, have business meetings, enjoy the lunch
        break or have a glass of wine after work. The smell of coffee and the friendly ambience
        will make every customer come back for more.</string>
    <string name="address_phil_coffee">Pitești Street, number 1, Cluj-Napoca</string>
    <string name="schedule_phil_coffee">Monday to Friday from 8 AM to 6 PM</string>
    <string name="phone_number_phil_coffee">+40 364 738 377</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
